38pitches.wordpress.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy | 38 Pitches

**38PITCHES.COM’S WEB SITE  
PRIVACY POLICY**

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how and for what purposes your personal information is being collected, processed and used. We pledge that we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information will only be used in ways that are in compliance with this Privacy Policy. **This Privacy Policy is only in effect for any web pages, e-mail lists, collective non user-specific information and collective personal information collected and/or owned on 38pitches.com’s and its affiliates’ (collectively, “38pitches.com,” “our,” or “we”) web sites, including but not limited to the**[ **www.38pitches.com**](http://www.38pitches.com/) **web site, as well as any online features, services and/or programs offered by 38pitches.com (collectively, the “Web Site”). Your use of the Web Site is also governed by Terms and Conditions [see the link on the Home page].**

**Please note that some of the information about yourself may be disclosed to WordPress.com. We encourage you to review and become familiar with the WordPress.com Privacy Policy (**[ **www.automattic.com/privacy/**](http://www.automattic.com/privacy/) **) in order to understand your obligations with respect to the information that you submit to WordPress.com. If you have any questions regarding your personal information submitted to WordPress.com, you should contact WordPress.com at**[ **www.wordpress.com/contact-support/**](http://www.wordpress.com/contact-support/) **.**

We will make an effort to update this web page with any changes to this Privacy Policy and you are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy frequently (the date of the most recent revision to this Privacy Policy appears at the end of this Privacy Policy).

**Use of Information**

Information collected by 38pitches.com is used for three main purposes. First, we collect information to improve the Web Site by determining which of our areas, features and forums are most popular. Second, we collect information to personalize the experience of the users of the Web Site. Finally, we collect information to enable our users to participate in features, services, programs and/or other activities from time to time.

You should understand that any information that you post to the Web Site, for any purpose and no matter of what nature or what medium or format, is considered to be a public disclosure and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Your UserID and the information that you deliver or post to the Web Site are included in your posts and submissions, but only to the extent that you affirmatively transmit such information. You should be aware that whenever you voluntarily post information to any public forum, whether on the Web Site or otherwise, the information that you post can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications of any form.

38pitches.com does not use its users email address or other personally identifiable information for commercial or marketing purposes without your consent or except as part of a program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. That being said, 38pitches.com may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes, for example to contact you.

In order to participate in many features, services and/or programs of the Web Site, we may require that you provide us with certain specific information, such as your full name, company information, mailing address, telephone number, e mail address, gender, personal interests and/or other information specific to you. You can choose whether or not to provide us with this information, but if you choose not to provide any required information, your experience on the Web Site may be diminished and some features may not be available or may not work as intended.

38pitches.com or a partner may sponsor promotions, sweepstakes or contests on the Web Site. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. 38pitches.com may also transfer personal information to certain advertising or marketing partners from whom you have requested to receive information.

**Additional Ways that Information is Collected**

**Browser Log Files**

Our servers automatically log each visitor to the Web Site and collect and record certain information about each visitor. This information includes your “Internet Protocol”, or IP, address, browser language, browser type, operating system, domain names, browsing history (including time spent at a domain, time and date of your visit), referring/exit web pages and URLs, and number of clicks.

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer’s IP address. When a user requests a web page from the Web Site, our web servers automatically recognize that user’s domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about the user other than the IP address from which the user has accessed the Web Site. We may use this information to examine our traffic in the aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of users.

**Cookies**

From time to time, 38pitches.com and/or our advertisers may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie, by itself, cannot read data from your hard disk or read cookie files created by other web sites. A cookie, by itself, does not damage your system. We may use cookies to identify and keep track of, among other things, those areas of the Web Site and third party web sites that you have visited in the past in order to enhance your next visit to the Web Site. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times that you have seen an advertisement. We and our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners and promotions that you see on the Web Site. You can choose whether or not to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. If you choose not to accept cookies, your experience on the Web Site may be diminished and some features may not be available or may not work as intended.

**When Information Is Disclosed By 38pitches.com**

In addition to the other times or occasions on which we might disclose information about users of the Web Site, we might also disclose information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a legal process and applicable laws; (b) enforce this Privacy Policy; (c) respond to claims that any materials, documents, images, graphics, logos, designs, audio, video and any other information provided from or on the Web Site violates the rights of third parties; or (d) protect the rights, property or personal safety of 38pitches.com, its users or the public.

We use reasonable precautions to keep the information that is disclosed to us secure. We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

38pitches.com does not use its users email address or other personally identifiable information for commercial or marketing purposes without your consent or except as part of a program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with third parties to demonstrate the usage patterns for 38pitches.com’s advertisements, content, functionality promotions and/or services on the Web Site.

We also reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information in connection with the enforcement of our Terms and Conditions [see the link on the Home page], take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the Web Site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of 38pitches.com, our users or others.

We reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information, as well as any other information, in connection with the sale or other disposition of all or part of the 38pitches.com business and/or assets. We also cannot make any representations regarding the use or transfer of your personally identifiable information or other information that we may have in the event of our bankruptcy, reorganization, insolvency, receivership or an assignment for the benefit of creditors. Furthermore, we cannot and will not be responsible for any breach of security by any third parties or for any actions of any third parties (including other users of the Web Site) that receive any of the information that is disclosed to us. The Web Site also links to a wide variety of other web sites and the Web Site may contain advertisements of third parties. We are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy policies of those web sites of third parties or how they treat information about their users, including those of WordPress.com and Automattic.com.

**Information From Children**

The Web Site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of thirteen (13). We do not collect personally identifiable data from any person that we know to be under the age of thirteen (13). You affirm that you are either more than 18 years of age, or an emancipated minor, or possess legal parental or guardian consent, and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in this Privacy Policy, and to abide by and comply with this Privacy Policy. In any case, you affirm that you are over the age of 13, as **THE WEB SITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR CHILDREN UNDER 13 THAT ARE UNACCOMPANIED BY HIS OR HER PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN**.

Parents should be aware that 38pitches.com’s Privacy Policy will govern our use of personal data, but also that information that is voluntarily given by children – or others – in chat sessions, e-mail exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited communications. 38pitches.com encourages all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal data while using the Internet.

**International Users**

Because 38pitches.com operates globally, the information that we collect may be made available to our affiliates, partners and subsidiaries worldwide. However, the Web Site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. For those users visiting us from the European Economic Area, Asia or any other non-United States location, please note that 38pitches.com may transfer your personally identifiable data outside the European Economic Area, China or the other non-United States location in which you are located for use for any of the purposes described above. By using the Web Site and providing 38pitches.com with your personal data, all users of the Web Site consent to such transfer of your personal data and that your use of the Web Site and any products or services offered by 38pitches.com is subject to the laws of the State of Delaware and the United States. All users of the Web Site agree and hereby submit to the exclusive personal jurisdiction of the state and federal courts located in the State of Delaware.

**Value Added Benefits**

We may request that you provide us with the personal information identified in the “Use of Information” Paragraph of this Privacy Policy for the purposes identified in that Paragraph. Whenever we request personal information from a user of the Web Site, we will make an effort to indicate the purpose of the inquiry at the time the information is requested. In order to provide users of the Web Site with many of the added values and special offers of reputable organizations and retailers, we may provide some or all of your personal information to reputable third party companies. Additionally, we may from time to time send e-mail to you announcing new features, services and/or programs offered through the Web Site. You may also receive mailings, telephone calls and/or facsimiles from other reputable, third-party companies. **Users have the option of not participating in these value added benefits by following the procedure for withholding your personal information that is set forth at the end of this Privacy Policy.**

When you create a User Account, UserID and password on the Web Site, and when you participate in any of the features, services and/or programs offered through the Web Site, we may request your full name, company information, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, gender, personal interests and/or other relevant information specific to you. This information will allow us to create your User Account and provide you with information that we believe will be important and relevant to you. This information may also be used by us to notify you of features, services and/or programs that may be of interest to you.

Whenever we collect personal information about you, we will make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

**Privacy Outside the Web Site**

The Web Site contains various links to other web sites, including links to various third party service providers. 38pitches.com is not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any of those other web sites. Other than under agreements with certain reputable organizations and companies, and except for third party service providers whose services you voluntarily elect to utilize, we do not share any of the personal information that you provide to us with any of the web sites to which the Web Site links, although we may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable data with those other web sites. Please check with those web sites in order to determine their privacy policies and your rights under them.

**Choices With Your Personal Information**

 Whether you submit personally identifiable information to 38pitches.com is entirely up to you. You may decide not to submit personally identifiable information through the Web Site, in which case 38pitches.com may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct information that you have submitted to 38pitches.com by contacting us as indicated at the end of this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions regarding your personal information submitted to WordPress.com, you should contact WordPress.com at [www.wordpress.com/contact-support/](http://www.wordpress.com/contact-support/). Please note that any information that you post, upload or transmit to 38pitches.com and/or the Web Site cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms and Conditions [see the link on the Home page].

**Your Consent To This Privacy Policy**

By using the Web Site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as specified above or as we otherwise see fit unless you inform us otherwise by means of the procedure identified below. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will make an effort to post those changes on this web page so that you will always be able to understand what information we collect, how we use that information and under what circumstances we may disclose that information to others. Your use of the Web Site following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. We may use comments, information or feedback that you may submit in any manner that we may choose without notice or compensation to you.

If you have additional questions or comments of any kind, if you see anything on the Web Site that you think is inappropriate, please let us know by e-mail or by sending your comments or requests to:

38pitches.com  
5 Clock Tower Place  
Maynard, Massachusetts 01754  
Attn: Customer Care – Privacy Issues  
(978) 310-5100  

Copyright © 2007. 38pitches.com. All Rights Reserved.

EFFECTIVE AS OF: MARCH 20, 2007  
LAST UPDATED: MARCH 28, 2007
